

### CONTACT

Baku, Azerbaijan

+79104623906 (What's app only)

nikita8192@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/nikita-nefedov

github.com/nefedovnd

### **SKILLS**

- Data analysis
- MS Excel
- **Pvthon** (machine, deep learning)
- SQL
- Tableau
- STATA
- Financial audit
- Analytical reports
- Presentations
- MS Powerpoint
- Political science
- Public opinion
- Survey analysis
- Scientific research
- Project management
- Design visualization
- 2D/3D Adobe

### LANGUAGES

English: fluent

German: basic (in progress)

Russian: native

# Nikita Nefedov

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Initiative, responsible and time-managing person with a range of practical and theoretical experience in the data analysis and financial control. Academically qualified in politics, public opinion and data analysis. Experienced in working in extreme conditions, able to dive into any topic in the shortest possible time with high attention to detail, carry out in-depth work on project management, conduct analytical reports and presentations.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Head Financial Control Directorate - Moscow, Russia 2/2021 - 11/2022 Advisor of an expert and analytical department 7/22 - 11/22Senior Specialist of the Department of Expert Analytical Activities 11/21 - 7/22

Leading Specialist of the Department of Expert Analytical Activities

- Data analysis and financial audit.
- Implementation of control in the financial and budgetary sphere, procurement, social sector (healthcare, urban construction, education).
- Conduction of anti-corruption and anti-monopoly investigations.
- Evaluation of the effectiveness of the disposal of organizations of their budgetary funds.
- Political, legislative and legal analysis.

## **Moscow City Innovation Agency - Moscow, Russia**

10/2020 - 12/2020

7/21 - 11/21

Intern

- Consulting in the field of technology development and innovative entrepreneurship.
- Monitoring of the innovation market and development of plans for cooperation with key partners.
- Organization of industry forums.

### **UN Online Volunteering service - Colchester, England**

4/2019 - 6/2019

Volunteer

Participated in development of Tanzanian infrastructure, managed IT software.

### **EDUCATION**

### University of Essex - Colchester, England

2014 - 2019

**Master of Arts:** Public Opinion and Political Behaviour (with distinction)

2018 - 2019

- Dissertation project has a first-class mark "Survey analysis of individual economic perception effect on public attitudes towards immigration and variation of attitudes across social classes."
- Qualification modules include: Public Opinion and Political Behaviour, Quantitative Political analysis, Data analysis, Survey analysis, Conflict Resolution, International Negotiations, Theory and Explanation in Political Science

#### **Bachelor of Arts:** Political Science

2015 - 2018

- Average mark: 2.1
- President of the University Society (2 terms)

Foundation Degree: Politics 2014 - 2015

### **CERTIFICATES**

Python / SQL data analysis • Python data science • Python machine learning / deep **learning with tensor flow • Tableau** full list at: linkedin.com/in/nikita-nefedov/details/certifications